Hello Hello friend, welcome to my
YouTube channel Financial Freedom. I am
Manish Tiwari, Financial Advisor. Today we will talk
about the motor insurance plan which has been recently launched by ASI,
whose name is Motor Insurance. Till now
you had heard of Family Floater only in health insurance
and this is your first time hearing about
motor insurance, so all of you stay tuned to
go till the end of my video.
And yes, if
you have not yet subscribed to my channel, then
subscribe to the channel and do
not forget to press the bell icon so that you can get the
notification of my videos first and yes, do like and
comment.
A bullet train fare, you have understood that this is Motor
Floater Insurance. From where has this term been taken?
What used to happen in Family Scooter Insurance with Family Floater was that once you used to
secure four more of your family members, in the
same way,
in your motor insurance, you will have four more family members under a single policy. Out of
its three
benefits, one will be insurance, second will be
special discount and third will be commission party.
Here you need to pay attention  The thing is that
you have to pay a lot of attention to two points, first you
need a single donor, on the other hand it is
necessary to have a private company and a private car,
and here you have to have only one
car, from which you can have four cars and Banaras
University, now here I will
tell you the three points separately,
you are seeing
that tax minute use, you understand that 2014, your four
vehicles should not be stuck at the same, you will get special
discount, but
on that patent, soldiers
go to Rajasthan, the ride point is compressive and
third party, what about this, whatever you do and in this
process, if you want, you should
take very less pressure, you
can also take both by clicking for third party, if your
program is press, bike, scooter,
partially, then you will get that powder love,
I want to tell you in a pimpled manner, how the
premium tax has also been added,
in this you have a private car which is
expiring tomorrow and two wheeler, that is, the
bike which is expiring in August, mix it
in December, then the basic school which is expiring in August,
its date from August to tomorrow will be
covered and medium tax plate will be done, take the
second bike in December, go and take it  If you can see that you will be
appointed as P then you will send the
amount of your three living expenses to the club and after totaling it,
cent percent
side effect will be calculated on it that you get the
premium and
male voter award that it is
not available online right now, to get it you will have to
meet the advisors from SSC Lamba,
either you can go to the office
or you can contact me by calling my helpline number, this is the
first such company in India, that is why it has
launched motor insurance for motor, if you have
four-five minutes, then you should
take incomplete insurance of motor footer, then you
will save a lot here and
you will get the benefit of special discount, if you
want that I will recommend you, then you
can definitely call the application number in the description box given below or you
can WhatsApp, if you
liked my video then
definitely press the button to tell your friends and yes, do
not forget to subscribe to my channel so that you can get the
notification of my videos first,
thank you for watching my video